Marion Toms Papers 2013.0022
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
Marion Toms Papers
undated, 1911-1985
2013.0022
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
0.15 Linear feet
Marion Toms was a life long resident of East Hartford, Connecticut. The collection contains personal and family materials dated 1911-1985.
Toms, Marion
Related Material
Archives & Special Collections has a substantial collection of materials pertaining to various aspects of Connecticut residents and history. For detailed information on these collections please contact the curator or ask at the Reading Room desk.
Provenance and Acquisition
The collection was donated in 2013 by Ms. Toms' family.
Access
The collection is open and available for research.
Biography
Marion Toms was born on 16 May 1911 in Wethersfield, Connecticut. The daughter of a postal inspector who was active in the Connecticut Republican Party, Ms. Toms attended school in East Hartford before her employment as a secretary in a law firm. Ms. Toms served as a drive during World War II and was a member of the South Congregational Church in East Hartford, Connecticut.
Scope and Contents
The collection contains personal and family documentation pertaining to Ms. Toms. Included in the collection are her high school student newspaper and yearbook, photographs, clippings, correspondence and publications.
Warder, Nancy L.; Clippings (information artifacts).; Connecticut; Correspondence; Newspapers; Periodicals; Personal papers; Photographs
- Series I: Personal papers, undated, 1911-1985
  - Baby book, 1911 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, undated, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, undated, 1920, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Janus, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Journal of the 39th Annual Convention, Woman's Relief Corps, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - PEN, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Toms family genealogy and history, undated, 1941, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - New Era, 1927-1928 (Oversize 1)
  - Family genealogies, undated (Oversize 1)